# Julie Sandoval

**Production Artist** 

### **♣** Profile

Experienced and dedicated production design professional offering over 22 years of loyal service to leading advertising and production operations, always going above and beyond expectations. Being detail-oriented, accurate and organized, my goal is to consistently deliver precision material with a high level of quality. Adaptable with a willingness to learn while maintaining a fearless demeanor throughout change. Friendly team member with high ethical standards who believes that fairness and equality are the basis for job satisfaction.

# Employment History

## **Digital Prepress Technician at Color Reflections**

January 2019 — March 2020

Prepared files for large format printing, consisting of large photographic prints, trade show graphics, floor graphics, wall graphics, wall wraps, window signage and various banners. Created custom cut files as well as color matching for assorted materials including fabric, vinyl, metal and plexiglass, to name a few. Worked closely with Customer Service Reps to fulfill clients needs. Have base knowledge of Print Press operations.

## Production Artist at B&P Advertising

September 2009 — December 2016

Served as marketing campaign's production, including various complex detailed artwork pertaining to high-end invitations, ads, billboards, and various print collateral. Achieved high standards of productivity, quality and efficiency throughout production department.

# Senior Graphic Artist at The Glenn Group

March 2000 — June 2009

Served as primary leader of critical marketing campaign's production, including several complex details of artwork. Headed production for all clients. Drove high standards of productivity, quality and efficiency throughout production art department.

#### Education

Continuing Education, College of Southern Nevada

September 2020 — Present

Associates/Graphics Technology, College of Southern Nevada

**HS Diploma, White Pine High School** 

#### **Contact**

702.604.3426

jmaesandoval@hotmail.com

#### **Skills**

Computer Skills

Adobe InDesign

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

Ability to Multitask

Fast Learner

Ability to Work Under Pressure

Ability to Work in a Team